{
    "id": "7fabaef431fa46698ab26052fa6df8bc",
    "title": "Elder, older, eldest, oldest",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "2fd31413fe584eb69cacaffd4951a104",
            "title": "Elder, Eldest, Older, Oldest",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "I am visiting my …………….. sister tomorrow.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "elder",
                        "older",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Julie is five years ………………… than me.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "elder",
                        "older",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "My …………………. brother is a pilot.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "elder",
                        "older",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I have two .....................… sisters.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "elder",
                        "older",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "His …………………. son works abroad.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "eldest",
                        "oldest",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "My grandmother is the ..................... member of my family.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "eldest",
                        "oldest",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "She is the …………………. student in her class.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "oldest",
                        "eldest",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "His ..................... son is a journalist.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "eldest",
                        "oldest",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "He is the ………………….. in the family.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "eldest",
                        "oldest",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "She is a couple of years ……………….. than him.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "elder",
                        "Either could be used here",
                        "older"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}